Nittyansh Srivastava

Software Developer

+91 8957525319 nittyanshns@gmail.com Raebareli, India 229127

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Skilled multitasker with a superior work ethic and good teamwork, problem-solving, and organizational skills. Willing to take on any task to help the team. Reliable and dedicated team player with hard working and resourceful approach. Hardworking Student offering part-time work experience and extensive knowledge of the core subject matter.

WORK HISTORY

Student Intern, June 2023 - Current (Oasis - Ghaziabad, India)

- Gained operational knowledge and supported departmental needs.
- Reported back to the instructor to receive day-to-day tasks and responsibilities.
- Communicated effectively with faculty and staff and accepted critiques and suggestions for areas of improvement.
- Planned, prepared, and participated in weekly meetings and events.

Student Intern, September 2022 - October 2022 (Shapemyskills - Ghaziabad, India)

- Gained operational knowledge and supported departmental needs.
- Provided project progress updates and proposed solutions to issues.
- Participated in workshops and presentations related to projects to gain knowledge.

EDUCATION

Ajay Kumar Garg Engineering College

Bachelor of Technology Computer Science And Engineering (December 2020 - Current)

Indian Institute of Technology Madras Madras

Bachelor of Science in Programming And Data Science (May 2021 - Current)

SKILLS

Team collaboration

Problem-solving

Project support

Algorithms and data structures

Python

Java Programmer

MS Office

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Collaborated with a team of 4 in the development of an Algorithm Visualizer Web development project

Supervised a team of 3 staff members.

Developed a Desktop Assistant with the help of my instructor during my Python Internship in ShapeMySkills